Seth Walton

(785)-766-6581 sdwalton83@gmail.com 111 S Janell Dr. Olathe, KS 66061 https://wmadhatterw.github.io/Portfolio/https://github.com/wmadhatterw https://www.linkedin.com/in/seth-walton-4b6399144/

Career Summary

I was born and raised in Concordia Kansas. My father started my passion into anything technology. I have been the family / friend tech guy since I was probably 13. I have been self employed the last 8 years or so doing hardware repair. Now I wish to Start A new Career in the Software Development Field. That will allow me to apply my current skills and further my education in the field of technology.

Skills

Visual Basic, X-Code, Swift, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, jQuery, BootStrap, Firebase, LabView, Windows and Mac Platforms, Microsoft Office, Digital Electronics, PC technology, Network Concepts, Electronic Communications, Electronic Devices, Microprocessors, Signal generators, Multi-meters, Soldering, Team Viewer Remote Desktop, Working with clients to Troubleshoot/Diagnose and Repair their hardware/software issues. Maintaining Good Customer Support for Return Business. Educating Customers on how to properly use their Electronics.

Experience

OWNER/OPERATOR, WALTON ELECTRONICS - 2008-PRESENT

Run an Electronics repair shop. Repair electronics, computers, and mobile devices. Install networks and electronics. Supply yearly Computer Remote Desktop/repair contracts.

HARDWARE TECHNICIAN, NATIONAL INSTRUMENTS – 2005-2007

Research and Development of Pxi/Vxi, Pci-e RIO Controllers. Soldered and repaired our prototype controllers. Designed PCBs and researched and installed new components for the PCBs of both VXI and PXI platforms.

LAB ASSISTANT, ITT TECH - 2003-2005

Assisted and taught students in Programing classes, AC/DC electronics, PLC classes. Was Network Administrator Assistant as well. Installed New Network and computers in the whole school.

Education

KU EDWARDS CAMPUS, Overland Park KS - Full Stack Web Development. 2017-2018

ITT TECHNICAL INSTITUTE, Austin TX – Computer and Electronics Engineering (AAS) Graduated Highest Honors, GPA 3.9

2003-2005